Preliminary Guide to the Takey Crist Papers, 1944-2002 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession, 2004 (2004-0098), 27 Boxes
  - Personal Files Series
    - Personal Correspondence, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Professional Research, Inc. (Box 2)
    - Report Cards, 1944-1955 (Box 2)
    - Scholarship Application (Box 2)
    - Wake Forest School of Medicine (Box 2)
    - Washington, D.C. - Medical Licenses (Box 2)
  - UNC Subject Files Series
    - Abortion and the College Student (Box 2)
    - Abortion Counseling and Psychiatric Illness with the Patient (Box 2)
    - Abortion R. D. (Box 2)
    - Abortion Equipment, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
    - Abortion Ethics (Box 2)
    - Abortion, Fetal Indication (Box 2)
    - Abortion, Hale Harvey Clinic - New York (Box 2)
    - Abortion and the Law (Box 2)
    - Abortion: Legislative Reform (Box 2)
    - Abortion Letters UNC (Box 3)
    - Abortion Letters, undated (Box 3)
    - Abortion Letters Jacksonville (Box 3)
    - Abortion Letters Book (Box 3)
    - Abortion: Medical and Psychological View (Box 3)
    - Abortion New York (Box 3)
    - Abortion and Nurses (Box 3)
    - Abortion (Original Research at the UNC Done by Dr. Crist & Dr. Palumbo) (Box 3)
    - Abortion Out-Patient (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Paper by Bruce Bowers, UNC Student 1971 (Box 3)
    - Abortion Position Paper (Box 3)
    - Abortion Preterm Clinic (Box 3)
    - Abortion and Psychiatry (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Psychiatric Letters (Box 3)
    - Abortion Research Study Group, CPC (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Resident Attended (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Saline Induction complications (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Senate Committee of North Carolina (Box 3)
    - Abortion Septic (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Status in US in 1972 (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Statistics in North Carolina (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Suction and Curettage (Box 3)
    - Abortions - Therapeutic NCMH Complications and Infirmary (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Topics, Dr. Crist's (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Topics for Discussion, Testimony, Statements (Box 3)
    - Abortion Topics, letters (Box 3)
    - Abortion - Topic Talk (Box 3)
    - Abortion - TV Show UNC, 1970, May 28 (Box 3)
    - Abortions - UNC Co-Ed (Box 3)
    - Abortions - where to get them (Box 3)
    - Abortions - where to get them - Eastern Women's Center, NYC (Box 3)
    - Abortions - where to get them - Park East Hospital (Box 3)
    - Abortions - where to get them - Parkmed, NYC (Box 3)
    - Abortions - where to get them -Women's Medical Center, DC (Box 3)
    - Abortion 1970 Style - Talk to Coeds (Box 3)
    - Abortion 1971 (Box 3)
    - Abortion, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Adolescence, suicide and (Box 5)
    - Anti-Abortionists (Box 5)
    - Artificial Insemination (Box 5)
    - ASA Material from New York [Association for the Study of Abortion] (Box 5)
    - Birth - Ideas of Births by College Students (Box 5)
    - Birth Control Information 1972 (Box 5)
    - Birth Control - Information on birth control with regard to teenagers (Box 5)
    - Cancer - Cervix (Box 5)
    - Cancer - CIS (Box 5)
    - Cancer - Ovary (Box 5)
    - Cancer - Vagina (Box 5)
    - Cancer - Vulva (Box 5)
    - Cancer - exenterative surgery, UNC (Box 5)
    - Cancer Patients - Wake Memorial Hospital (Box 5)
    - Carolina Population Center - Books Available (Box 5)
    - Circumcision (Box 5)
    - Clinic, Model for Cabarrus County (Box 5)
    - Clinic, Model for Winston Salem (Box 5)
    - Clinic - Teenage for Cabarrus County (Box 5)
    - Clinic, Teenage, Chapel Hill, N.C. (Box 5)
    - Clinics, Handouts for Teenage Clinics (Box 5)
    - Clinics, teenage - how to set up (Box 5)
    - Coed - Information and Sex (Box 5)
    - Coed Living and Student Rights (Box 5)
    - Coed - Politics and (Box 6)
    - Coed Questionnaires (Box 6)
    - Contraceptives (Box 6)
    - Contraception - Attitudes on contraception, Steven Polgar (Box 6)
    - Contraception - College Student and (Box 6)
    - Contraception - Psychology of (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, Personal (Box 6)
    - Dalkon Shield - Work with Dennis Johnson (Box 6)
    - Dalkon Shield - study of Colorado State Univ. Student (Box 6)
    - Dalkon Shield Study (Box 6)
    - Dalkon Shield Study - reprints (Box 6)
    - Dalkon Shield and Urinary Tract Infections, Study of (Box 7)
    - Drugs - Abuse (Box 7)
    - Drugs and College Students (Box 7)
    - Drugs and Teenagers (Box 7)
    - E&B: Medical Students Summer Research Program (Box 7)
    - E&B: the Sex Men (Box 7)
    - E&B: Drafts (Box 7)
    - E&B: References (Box 7)
    - E&B: Formal Talk (Box 7)
    - E&B: Final Report (Box 7)
    - E&B: Distribution (Box 7)
    - E&B. Correspondence (Box 7)
    - E&B: Promotional Letters (Box 7)
    - E&B. Complaint File (Box 7)
    - E&B Reference Letters (Box 7)
    - E&B. - requests, undated (Box 7)
    - E&B, Requests and Correspondence, 1970 (Box 7)
    - E&B, Requests and Correspondence, Jan.-March 1971 (Box 8)
    - E&B, Requests and Correspondence, April-June, 1971 (Box 8)
    - E&B, Requests and Correspondence, July-Sept. 1971 (Box 8)
    - E&B, Requests and Correspondence, Oct.-Dec.1971 (Box 8)
    - E&B, Requests and Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 8)
    - Elephants and Butterflies, 1977 (Box 8)
    - E&B, Requests and Correspondence, 1979, 1980s (Box 8)
    - E&B: Ann Painter (Box 8)
    - E&B: Interviews (Box 8)
    - E&B: background material (Box 8)
    - E&B: Pregnancy and Masturbation (Box 8)
    - E&B: Sterility and Abortion (Box 8)
    - E&B: The Pill, the Loop (Box 9)
    - E&B - Homosexuality, Venereal Disease (Box 9)
    - E&B - Questionnaire on population and reproduction (Box 9)
    - E&B. Proposed Price Change (Box 9)
    - E&B: Correspondence with Harcourt Brace Jovanovich (Box 9)
    - E&B: Internal Correspondence and Paperwork on Revisions (Box 9)
    - E&B - Editions 2, 3, 4 (Box 9)
    - Elephants and Butterflies - 2nd Edition (Box 9)
    - Elephants and Butterflies - 3rd Edition (Box 9)
    - Elephants and Butterflies - 3rd Edition, 2nd Printing (Box 9)
    - Elephants and Butterflies - 3rd Edition, 3rd Printing, Plain (Box 9)
    - Elephants and Butterflies - 3rd Edition, 3rd Printing, Marshall University (Box 9)
    - E&B. Changes for 4th (Box 9)
    - E&B. Changes for 6th printing (Box 9)
    - E&B. Wake Forest Edition (Box 9)
    - Elephants and Butterflies - India Edition (Box 9)
    - E&B - Sex and College Students, Dean Fredrick A. Dobens, Colgate Univ. (Box 9)
    - Elephants and Butterflies, Supplemental Inserts (Box 9)
    - E&B: Meredith Webb Printing, Correspondence, Invoices, etc. (Box 9)
    - E&B: Accounting from UNC Stores, Sales (Box 9)
    - E&B: Permission File (Box 9)
    - E&B: Nelson and Company (Box 9)
    - E&B DTH Column Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 9)
    - E&B DTH Column, 1971 (Box 9)
    - E&B DTH Column, 1972 (Box 9)
    - E&B DTH Column, Extra Copies (Box 9)
    - E&B DTH Column Questions on Elephants and Butterflies, Daily Tar Heel (Box 9)
    - E&B DTH Column Universal Press Syndicate (Box 9)
    - E&B DTH Controversy (Box 9)
    - Endometrosis - paper on Boom's (Box 10)
    - Epinephrine Experiment (Box 10)
    - Epinephrine, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Epinephrine, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Family Planning Task Force Raleigh, 3 March 1971 (Box 10)
    - Friends for Sex (Box 10)
    - Grant (Box 10)
    - Grant - Application for University Research Council (Box 10)
    - Grant - N.C. Regional Medical Program (Box 10)
    - Grant - Request to NIH for morning-after-treatment (Box 10)
    - Grant - Sex (Box 10)
    - Grant - Task Force for Sex Education (Box 10)
    - HEED 33 Correspondence (Box 10)
    - HEED 33 Topics (Box 10)
    - HEED 33 Course Outline (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Introduction (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Presentation to Class (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Spring 1972 (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Fall 1972 (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Spring 1973 (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Spring 1973 Takey Crist's Presentation (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Work with Bill Griffin (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Bibliography (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Reprints for (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Venereal Disease (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Homosexuality, papers by Jodi Friedman (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 Variations of Human Sexual Behavior (Box 11)
    - HEED 33 - Sociological Study of Students in Topics in Human Sexuality (Box 11)
    - Health Education Clinic Coeds UNC (Box 11)
    - Health Education Clinic - Finances (Box 11)
    - Hendricks, Dr. Charles H. (Box 11)
    - Heusner, Albert Price - Papers, ideas of writing a paper or book (Box 11)
    - HEW Family Planning Consulting (Box 12)
    - Hospital, Wake County (Box 12)
    - Hospital, Watts (Box 12)
    - Hospital, Winston-Salem (Box 12)
    - Human Sexuality (Box 12)
    - Human Sexuality - Outlines (Box 12)
    - Human Sexuality - Committee for Human Sexuality, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Human Sexuality - Committee for Human Sexuality, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Human Sexuality Information and Counseling Service (Box 12)
    - Human Sexuality - Questions from College Students (Box 12)
    - Human Sexuality -- Research Paper by Howard Stang (Box 12)
    - Intercourse (Box 13)
    - Intercourse, anal (Box 13)
    - Intercourse, pre-marital (Box 13)
    - Intercourse, statistics (Box 13)
    - Interviews Coeds (Box 13)
    - Kidder Organization, Inc. (Box 13)
    - Kinsey Institute (Box 13)
    - Lactation following Lobectomy (Box 13)
    - Lactation Study (Box 13)
    - Laminaria Tent (Box 13)
    - Law (Box 13)
    - Law, Contraception and the (Box 13)
    - Law, Teenagers and the Pill (Box 13)
    - Love Clinic (Box 13)
    - Luitweiler, Dr. J.C. (Box 13)
    - Magazine Article - Emergence Medical Magazine (Box 14)
    - Magazine Article - Medical World News, Dec. 18, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Magazine Article - Sexual Behavior Magazine (Box 14)
    - Magazine Article - Time Magazine, Joyce Leviton (Box 14)
    - Magazine Article - Today's Health (Box 14)
    - Marfan's Syndrome (Box 14)
    - Marriage, Material on (Box 14)
    - Masters and Johnson (Box 14)
    - Medical Peer Review (Box 14)
    - Meeting - 1968, March 27-30, Fertility Sterility Meeting, San Francisco (Box 14)
    - Meeting - 1970, Sept. 27-30, Training for Sex, Marriage & Family Planning Counseling (Box 14)
    - Meeting - 1971, May 1-5, San Francisco, Family Life Sex Education Program (Box 14)
    - Meeting - 1971, May 3-7, San Francisco, ACOG (Box 14)
    - Meeting - 1971, Sept. 24-27, American Fertility/Sterility Society (Box 14)
    - Meeting - 1971, Nov. 5, SIECUS, 2nd annual conference (Box 14)
    - Meeting - 1971, Dec. 6, Univ. of Pennsylvania, Sex and the College Student (Box 14)
    - Meeting - 1972, Feb. 3-4, HEW Workshop - Rockville, MD (Box 14)
    - Meeting - 1972, April 30-May 4, ACOG, Chicago (Box 14)
    - Meeting - 1972, Aug. 5-12, San Francisco, CA, Sexual Education Course, Glide Foundation (Box 15)
    - Meeting - 1972, Sept., Carolina Population Center (Box 15)
    - Meeting - 1972, Oct. 22-24, ACOG, District IV, Atlanta, GA (Box 15)
    - Merrell Drug Study - Correspondence (Box 15)
    - Morning After Pill - Trick or Treatment (Box 15)
    - Morning After Treatment (Box 15)
    - Morning After Treatment - Abott Laboratories (Box 15)
    - Morning After Treatment - NIH, Feb. 14, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Morning After Treatment - NC Data (Box 15)
    - Morning After Treatment Study (Box 15)
    - Morning After Treatment - Study Data (Box 16)
    - Morning After Treatment Paper, NCMJ, 1973 (Box 16)
    - Morning After Treatment, Philips - Roxane Labs (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Article - Bangor Daily News (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Article - Duke Chronicle (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Article - Greensboro Daily News, Earnhardt (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Article - Greensboro Daily News, Nov. 14, 1971 (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Article - Medical School Bulletin News (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Article - Miss Eileen Milling (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Articles - New York Times (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Article - Thomasville Newspaper (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Article - University News Bureau (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Article - Winston Salem Journal (Box 16)
    - Nurses, New Concepts for (Box 16)
    - Ob/Gyn Fellowship Programs (Box 16)
    - Operations, 1969 (Box 16)
    - Operations, 1970 (Box 16)
    - Operations, 1971 (Box 16)
    - Operations, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Orgasm (Box 16)
    - Ortho Panel on Sex (Box 16)
    - Ortho Pharmaceutical Corporation (Box 16)
    - Out-Patient Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 16)
    - Paper - Abortion: Where Have we Been? Where Are We Going? (Box 16)
    - Paper - The Coed as Gyn Patient (Box 16)
    - Paper - Diet and Pregnancy (Box 17)
    - Paper - Drug Mimic toxemia (Box 17)
    - Paper - Influence of Maternal Epinephrine on Behavior of Offspring (Box 17)
    - Paper - Life Change and Illness Susceptibility (Box 17)
    - Paper - Primary Carcinoma of the Fallopian Tube (Box 17)
    - Paper -- Stress During Gestation and Offspring Behavior (Box 17)
    - Paper -- Tay-Sachs Disease (Box 17)
    - Pathology - UNC Medical School (Box 17)
    - Patient Letters for book (Box 17)
    - Patient Notes (Box 17)
    - Patients, 1971 (Box 17)
    - Patients, 1972 (Box 17)
    - Patients, Fertility Sterility (Box 17)
    - Patients, Coed, UNC (Box 17)
    - Pediatrics, 1964-1965 (Box 18)
    - Pelvic Congestion - Selig Neubardt (Box 18)
    - Philosophy in Medicine (Box 18)
    - Philosophy on OB-GYN (Box 18)
    - Physical Therapy Lecture (Box 18)
    - Planned Parenthood - College Program (Box 18)
    - Population Services, Inc. (Box 18)
    - Post-Coital Questions (Box 18)
    - Premarital Medical Exam (Box 18)
    - Problem Pregnancy - Research done by Robert Wilson (Box 18)
    - Prolapse Cords (Box 18)
    - Psychiatry, 1962-1963 (Box 18)
    - Psychiatry, 1963-1964 (Box 19)
    - Psychiatry Reprints (Box 19)
    - Psychiatry, Role of Telephone Interview - Sensitivity (Box 19)
    - Reading List, Senior Year, Medicine Dept. (Box 19)
    - Reprint - The Abortion Argument: What it's not about (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Abortion and Promise Keeping (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Adenoacanthoma Originating in Endometriosis of the Ovary (Box 19)
    - Reprint -- Birth Defects (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Coronary Artery Aneurysm (Box 19)
    - Reprint - The Doctor Talks About Menopause (Box 19)
    - Reprint - The Doctor Talks about Menstruation (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Family Planning and the Pharmacist (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Methapyrilene Toxic Psychosis Mimicking Eclampsia (Box 19)
    - Reprint - The Pill and the Teenage Girl (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Primary Carcinoma of the Fallopian Tube (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Problems of Menstruation (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Questions Everyone Asks About Sex (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Scientific American (Box 19)
    - Reprints - Selected Statistics on the Population Problem (Box 19)
    - Reprints - Semantic Aspects of Abortion (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Sex, Love and Intimacy - Whose Life Styles? (Box 19)
    - Reprints - Sex, Sexuality, and Sexual Love (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Something is Happening on Our College Campuses (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Stress Incontinence and the Nulliparous Patient (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Stress Incontinence of Urine (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Surgical Management of Tubal Pregnancy (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Teenage Pregnancy (Box 19)
    - Reprint - The Unwanted Pregnancy (Box 19)
    - Reprint - Urethrovesical Needle Suspension (Box 19)
    - Reprint - What Every woman should know about abortion (Box 19)
    - Ross, Robert A. Society, 29-31 Jan. 1970 (Box 19)
    - Ross, Robert A. Society, 1971 (Box 19)
    - Ross, Robert A. Society, 1972 (Box 19)
    - Sex, Articles, 1971 (Box 19)
    - Sex, Articles, 1972 (Box 19)
    - Sex, Articles, 1974 (Box 19)
    - Sex - Assistance for the Sexually Active Female (Box 19)
    - Sex Books on Campus - Points to Ponder (Box 20)
    - Sex - Cartoons and (Box 20)
    - Sex Center Information (Box 20)
    - Sex - the Coed and (Box 20)
    - Sex and College, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - Sex - the College Student and, Statistics (Box 20)
    - Sex Counseling and the Physician, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - Sex Education (Box 20)
    - Sex Education - Atlanta, GA, 1972 (Box 20)
    - Sex Education - Arizona State University (Box 20)
    - Sex Education - Cartoons for [Removed to OS Box 1.] (Box 20)
    - Sex Education - Center for the study of sex education in Medicine (Box 20)
    - Sex Education - College Information (Box 20)
    - Sex Education - Correspondence, undated, 1970 (Box 20)
    - Sex Education -- Correspondence, 1971 (Box 21)
    - Sex Education - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 21)
    - Sex Education - Drawings (Box 21)
    - Sex Education -- Greensboro (Box 21)
    - Sex Education - High school (Box 21)
    - Sex Education -- Homosexuality (Box 21)
    - Sex Education in Prison (Box 21)
    - Sex Education - Lectures and Curriculum (Box 21)
    - Sex Education - Paper by Gwen Brannon (Box 21)
    - Sex Education - Report to Dr. Friday, UNC (Box 21)
    - Sex Education - Ronald J. Pion's Paper: Family Planning Education (Box 21)
    - Sex Education Speech (Box 21)
    - Sex Education - Teenagers in Raleigh, N.C. (Box 21)
    - Sex Education - UNC Medical School (Box 21)
    - Sex Education, Visual Aids (Box 21)
    - Sex - Europe and (Box 22)
    - Sex - Impotency (Box 22)
    - Sex Information (Box 22)
    - Sex - Interview with Ethel Nash, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Sex - Menstruation (Box 22)
    - Sex and Mental Retardation (Box 22)
    - Sex Myths (Box 22)
    - Sex -- NCSU (Box 22)
    - Sex and old age (Box 22)
    - Sex - Papers for Coeds (Box 22)
    - Sex and Physicians (Box 22)
    - Sex and Pregnancy (Box 22)
    - Sex Projects, Correspondence (Box 22)
    - Sex Projects, Earl Harper, NC Personnel Dept. (Box 22)
    - Sex Project - Richmond VA (Box 22)
    - Sex Project - Univ. of Virginia (Box 22)
    - Sex - Prostaglandins (Box 22)
    - Sex - Reading Material for College (Box 22)
    - Sex References (Box 22)
    - Sex and Women in Prison (Box 22)
    - Sex Words (Box 22)
    - Sexual Behavior, Variations in (Box 22)
    - Sexual Revolution - Playboy Magazine (Box 22)
    - SIECUS (Box 22)
    - Speech - 1969, July 10, Raleigh N.C., Diet (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, 1971, Feb., East Carolina University Symposium (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, May, E.A. Tyler talk on sex in medical school (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, May 26, NC Emergency Room Association, Raleigh, Abortion (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, June 26, Duke, Abortion Lecture (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, July 29, Southern Obstetric and Gynecologic Seminar, Asheville, N.C., Abortion (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, Oct 1. and Nov. 15, Series: Sexual Problems in Medical Practice, Contraception, Crist & Hendricks (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, Oct. 3, Robert A. Ross Society (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, Oct. 8, Durham, N.C., Nurses of District 11 (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, Oct. 13, Sex Education Symposium (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, Oct. 14, Sex Education, Conner Dorm (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, Oct. 19, ACOG District IV, Charleston, S.C. (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, Nov. 2, Meredith College, Sex Symposium (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, Nov. 18, Medical Alumni Association, District V, New Bern (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1970, Dec. 3-6, South Dakota, Seminar on Sexuality (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, Jan. 20, Wilmington Medical Society (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, Jan. 21, Stratford College, VA (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, Jan.21, Coastal Plains OB-Gyn Society, Current Status of Abortion (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, Feb. 19, Duke University Divinity School (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, Feb. 23, Jacksonville Symposium (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, Feb. 24, Atlantic Christian College (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, March 1, WRAL TV (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, March 12-13, Southern College Health Association, Univ. of Georgia, Athens (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, March 22, Greensboro, N.C., Kiwanis Club, Abortion in N.C. (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, April 6-8, YMCA Symposium, Raleigh, NC (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, April 7, Pan Albemarle Medical Society (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, April 12-13, Westminster College (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, April 14-16, University of Maine Symposium (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, April 21-23, UNC-C, Population Conference (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, April 27, Greensboro College, Symposium (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, May 17, N.C. Medical Society (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, June 16, Greensboro Greater Chamber of Commerce (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, June 16-18, Academy of General Practitioners, Memphis, TN, Human Sexuality (Box 23)
    - Speech - 1971, Aug. 8, Community Church of Chapel Hill (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Aug. 27, UNC, Orientation Program (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Sept. 12, UNC postgraduate course, Waynesville, N.C. (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Sept. 29, Charlotte, N.C., The Young Carolinians (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Oct. 3, UNC Residence Hall, Morrison Sex Symposium (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Oct. 5 and 12, N.C. State University, Sex Symposium (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Oct. 11, Peace College, Raleigh, Psychology of Contraception (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Oct. 20, Clinical Symposium, Pharmacy School (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Oct. 26, Nurses District IV, Hampton Roads, VA (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Nov. 4, NJ Obstetrical and Gynecological Society (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Nov. 17, The Young Carolinians, Raleigh, N.C. (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Dec. 1, Student Pharmacy Association (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1971, Dec. 3, North Hampton Community College, Bethlehem, PA, Sex Ed Symposium (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, Jan.-March, UNC-C, Population Workshop (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, Jan. 6, Queens College (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, Jan. 18, Abortion Debate (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, Jan. 20, Wesleyan College (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, Jan. 25, Charlotte Writers' Club (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, Feb. 2, Rockingham Community College, Abortion and College Student (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, Feb. 10, Young Carolinians, Greensboro, NC (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, Feb. 25, Univ. of S.C. (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, March 1, Phiffer College, Misenheimer, NC (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, April 18-19, Sioux Falls, SD, Human Sexuality Meeting (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, April 20, Univ. of Colorado-Bolder,, Birth Control Conference (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, April 21, Planned Parenthood, Houston, TX (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, April 22, YMCA, Charlotte, N.C. (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, May 17, Young Carolinians, Charlotte, NC (Box 24)
    - Speech - 1972, May 5, Norfolk, Va, Teenage Pregnancy (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, May 7, Greensboro, N.C., Unitarian Church (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, May 10, Onslow County, Sex Education Program (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, May 23, Shelby, N.C., Medical Society (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, May 30, WGHP-TV, High Point, N.C. (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, May 30, Winston-Salem Medical Society, Sex Education (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, June 4, Kinston, N.C., Civic Organization (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, June 28, Greensboro, N.C., Chamber of Commerce (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, July 19, District V Nurses Association, Lumberton NC (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Aug. 25, UNC Orientation Program (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Sept. 11-13, NCSU, Human Sexuality Symposium (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Sept. 21, Community Health Association, Charlotte NC (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Sept. 27-29, Planned Parenthood League of Massachusetts (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Sept. 29, UNC, Problem Pregnancy Workshop (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Oct. 2, Ob/Gyn Society, Pittsburgh (Box 25)